I'm gonna use this as a backdrop
over what we gonna talk about.
And specifically I want to start with something
That was very decisive in our project.
Conversation about personality both that we should have.
I know that many sites.
Or many website owners...
Don't talk about personality.
But I think that if we want to stand out
it's the only change to stand out.
To be different, or stand out of the crowd.
And it kinda balls down to how we define
Websites as a part of our humanity.
Or the other way around...
That humanity is part of our websites.
So if I ask you now...
Can you think of a website
So memorable...
That is been so memorable over the last month or so
Or maybe two months
That's still in your head right now.
A website where you can say
Wow!
That was a memorable website.
Facebook... maybe?
But is there a website
That was so impact full on you.
Not necessary in terms of design.
But could be in terms of content.
That had a tremendous impact on you.
That really is stuck of you as of now.